<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="46" huntingZoneId="11" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="211" prevId="0" villagerId="1009">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="211" prevId="0" villagerId="1009">
        <Page social="4">If you're going to fraternize with the pirates, you need to do it right.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You need to talk and act like them if you expect to get any respect—by which I mean cooperation.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Convince {@LinkCreature:211#1036$$Dilato} and {@LinkCreature:62#1014$$Finn} that you're interested in being a pirate, and you'll have access to all kinds of information.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="211" prevId="2" villagerId="1036">
        <Page social="4">Nowadays it seems like everyone thinks they can just walk up and be a pirate! You think an eye patch and a funny bird are all it takes?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Tell you what—answer this question and we'll see if you've got the heart of a pirate.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When does a pirate start drinking rum?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="211" prevId="2" villagerId="1036">
        <Page social="4">Aye, that's about the time! You might just have a pirate's heart yet!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="211" prevId="2" villagerId="1036">
        <Page social="4">Indeed! Now that's an answer I can get behind! Cheers to the wee ones and their rum-soaked little hearts.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="62" prevId="3" villagerId="1014">
        <Page social="4">You look a little...hmm. You sure you're cut out for a pirate's life?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Well, let's see what you've got.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;What's the most exciting part of being a pirate?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7" huntingZoneId="62" prevId="3" villagerId="1014">
        <Page social="4">Ah, yes...I enjoy a pocket full of change myself! Well said, friend. I'll drink to that!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8" huntingZoneId="62" prevId="3" villagerId="1014">
        <Page social="4">The calm comfort of the water. Aye, that's something I enjoy myself. Well said.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9" huntingZoneId="62" prevId="3" villagerId="1014">
        <Page social="4">A real pirate's pirate! That's what you are!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="10" huntingZoneId="62" prevId="3" villagerId="1014">
        <Page social="4">Ha! Let's drink to drinking! That's definitely something worth drinking to. You may just be cut out for this after all.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="11" huntingZoneId="211" prevId="6" villagerId="1009">
        <Page social="4">Good job! Being recognized by the pirates is not an easy task.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Just do a few favors for them, and it won't be long before they take you in fully.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
