<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="1" huntingZoneId="743" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">You received a letter from the Mysterium requesting help. Your team entered the Wonderholme and defeated Bandersnatch and his noctenium-corrupted crew to rescue Aliss and the other scientists.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Dear &lt;PCName&gt;,&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I am Adonis, Maester of the Mysterium. In my haste to begin study on an immense castle built of noctenium, I may have sent my people into grave danger. My foremost noctenium expert, Aliss, and her associates are missing and I am unable to contact them or retrieve them by myself.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If your travels take you near Wonderholme in the Veritas District, would you help mount a rescue mission to retrieve my people?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;——Maester Adonis</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="743" prevId="2" villagerId="44435">
        <Page social="4">Don’t be fooled by my appearance. I was once a researcher of the Mysterium, until this cursed place transformed me into what you see now.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But if you didn't come here for me, why are you here?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&amp;quot;I got a letter, asking for my help.&amp;quot;&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Ah, you must be who Adonis spoke of. I have actually been waiting for you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;This place is Wonderholme. It's noctenium walls have created powerful beasts and fiendish traps.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We came to study the noctenium effects but the denizens were too powerful, and I ended up corrupted like them. The owner of the keep proclaimed himself king of the world, and took our chief scientist, Aliss, prisoner. Please free Aliss.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;As soon as you ascend the stairs, enemies will rush out to meet you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Keep your wits about you, and you will endure—and prevail!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Good luck!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="743" prevId="3" villagerId="44432">
        <Page social="0">Thank you so much.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If you had not come, I could not have rescued Aliss. The sorcerer seized noctenium belonging to the Mysterium. Getting it out of his hands is also important &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I hereby reward you for your service.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You've earned the title Defender of Science, which carries tremendous respect in the Mysterium.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Your accomplishment today will be forever remembered!</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
