<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="1" huntingZoneId="810" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">A small group of devas has discovered a secret prison, hidden within the Rift—a prison we believe contains only one inmate: the god Lakan.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We sent a squad of elite scouts to confirm this, but they had only just encountered the devas' leader, a sorceress named Risalke, before we lost contact with them.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The devas may not know whose prison they're disturbing—but Risalke almost certainly does. She cannot be allowed to steal Lakan's power—or worse still, release him. You must go and stop her.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You'll find the entrance to Lakan's prison west of Oblivion Woods.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="810" prevId="2" villagerId="510">
        <Page social="0">Over here...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Glad you made it. I'm the only one who survived. The rest of my comrades are dead—slain by the devas, or Risalke's bodyguard, Trolok.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You've got to stop Risalke. She's inside the prison right now, negotiating with Lakan—promising him freedom in exchange for power. If Lakan gets out—or even if she leaves with a fraction of his power—the whole world is doomed.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="59" prevId="3" villagerId="1009">
        <Page social="0">You've done it! You've saved the entire world.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;This may not be the only entrance to Lakan's prison, but we'll do our best to seal it shut, so this never happens again.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If we fail, though, I know we can count on you.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
