<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="21" huntingZoneId="478" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="73" prevId="0" villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="73" prevId="0" villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="4">Thulsa is dead, but the curse on the ouijic ore—that stuff from Mount Tyrannas—isn't fading.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We don't know why, but we do know this: if we don’t do anything about it, Kaidun's former soldiers will fall under the curse and attack Acarum.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You've dealt with this ouijic ore before, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. I wouldn't trust anyone else.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Happy to help."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="1">Check with Georrif here in Acarum.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;He knows a lot about ouijic ore.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="73" prevId="2" villagerId="1109">
        <Page social="4">Glad you're on the case, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. Remember Ghufran? The guy you rescued from the curse when you were tracking down Kaidun?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The mystery of the ore is a matter of personal honor to him. He's desperate to end the curse before anyone else suffers his fate.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Ghufran thinks that something else—something beyond our reach—is broadcasting power to the ouijic ore. The technical stuff is beyond me, but Ghufran can explain it. Head toward Mount Tyrannas, and you'll find Ghufran near the graveyard.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="73" prevId="3" villagerId="1116">
        <Page social="4">It is good to see you, &lt;PCNAME&gt;, though I'm still ashamed that you had to rescue me from the curse.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I've been carrying bits of ouijic ore across the countryside, trying to triangulate where it's drawing strength from. But it's not a "where." It's a "who."&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;An argon named Suryati lies beyond this teleportal. I tried to defeat Suryati myself, but once again, I was too weak.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It shames me to require your help again, but I don't want anyone else to suffer my fate. Use this scroll to head through the teleportal and defeat Suryati!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="73" prevId="4" villagerId="1501">
        <Page social="1">(The scroll activates the teleportal for you. The path to Suryati's Peak is now clear.)</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
