<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="4" huntingZoneId="72" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="72" prevId="0" villagerId="1448">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="72" prevId="0" villagerId="1448">
        <Page social="4">Hmm...you're going to need someone with an academic background, so you know what you're looking for in Sirjuka Gallery. I suppose that means I should go with you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If Thulsa left behind any traps, perhaps I can spot them. Like I said, hiding things wasn't Thulsa's specialty.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Gather your friends and meet me in Sirjuka Gallery.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="496" prevId="2" villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="4">Thulsa may have secretly siphoned power from the Core, then placed it in that crystal.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But the only way to know for sure is to examine the crystal more closely...&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"That's my cue, isn't it?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Yes, but getting it won't be easy. There's an ominous energy here, similar to how I felt in the laboratory.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The odds of Thulsa leaving that crystal unguarded by his dark magic? Vanishingly small.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What do we do?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Let's assume the crystal is trapped. Thulsa probably thought if he couldn't have it, neither could anyone else. Keeping the crystal safe is our first priority.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Jermir and I will stay clear of the crystal and assist you from a distance. Keep that crystal intact at all costs!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="72" prevId="3" villagerId="1448">
        <Page social="4">The crystal is intact! Now we can compare it to the Core's energy within Fraya and find out whether Thulsa's research was getting anywhere.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Tell Fraya what we've learned. It'll take some time to move the crystal, but I'll follow as soon as I can.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="518" prevId="4" villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="4">That's quite a tale, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. I wonder...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I wonder whether Jerad can reverse Thulsa's technique. Rather than dividing and corrupting the Core, perhaps it could stabilize and strengthen the Core within me. Certainly worthy of further study, don't you think?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;This matter is concluded, but remember: you accomplished your mission, but it remains strictly confidential. We don't want anyone "inspired" by Thulsa's research.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
