<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="2" huntingZoneId="72" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="518" prevId="0" villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="518" prevId="0" villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="4">Remember the name Malachai? The name Thulsa assumed while hiding in Allemantheia? Good.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Thulsa's reason for hiding among us was always obscure, but we may have figured it out.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Above all else, Thulsa wanted to regain the power he lost at the end of the Divine War. With the Mysterium's help, he was researching ways to siphon off the power of the Core or corrupt it entirely.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;At the time, Serion was the Core. But now I'm the Core, and I don't want Thulsa's research falling into the wrong hands.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"How do I fit in?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">After all we've been through, I trust you, &lt;PCNAME&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I am the Core now, and I don't want Thulsa's research to tempt the wrong people, whether they're gods or mortals.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'll be blunt. Someone might use Thulsa's research to control or corrupt me.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Is that likely?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">We elves are an ambitious people. Let's leave it at that.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;For more information on Malachai—I mean Thulsa—and his research, talk to a baraka named Jerad at the Sanctum Mysterium. He's an expert in the language of ancient gods and dragons, and should be helpful translating any research documents you find.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="72" prevId="2" villagerId="1448">
        <Page social="4">&lt;PCNAME&gt;?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Are you the outside help Commander Fraya mentioned?&lt;BR&gt;I wasn't expecting someone from the military, but no matter. I think Fraya trusts us precisely because we are outside Allemantheia's power structure.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let me explain what I've learned so far.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Go ahead."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Malachai—pardon me, Thulsa—was trying to divide the power of the Core into multiple quantities.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Fraya doesn't talk about elven politics, but that's why she's worried. Imagine the elves fighting over how to divide up the Core's power. It would tear this city apart!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Malachai told the Mysterium that the research was a dead end, but we now know he had ulterior motives.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Now certain factions among the elves are asking for access to Malachai's laboratory, so we have to act fast.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Malachai's Lab?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Ever since Malachai revealed himself to be Thulsa, his lab has been off limits. Even the Mysterium hasn't been in there.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But when you're the Core, you don't hear the word "no" a lot. Fraya obtained access for us. My assistant, Armis, can send you to Malachai's Lab.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You won't have much time in there—we don't want to attract attention—so please search as quickly as you can.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="72" prevId="3" villagerId="1450">
        <Page social="4">Do not linger! Search through Thulsa's research as quickly as you can.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Prepare yourself, and when you're ready, I'll send you to the lab.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;font color='#FF0000'&gt;Only one person can enter Malachai's Lab.&lt;/font&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="72" prevId="3" villagerId="1450">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="72" prevId="3" villagerId="1450">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="7" huntingZoneId="72" prevId="3" villagerId="1450">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="8" huntingZoneId="72" prevId="3" villagerId="1450">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="9" huntingZoneId="72" prevId="3" villagerId="1450">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="10" huntingZoneId="72" prevId="3" villagerId="1450">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="11" huntingZoneId="72" prevId="3" villagerId="1450">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="12" huntingZoneId="72" prevId="3" villagerId="1450">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="13" huntingZoneId="428" prevId="3" villagerId="1007">
        <Page social="4">This experimental journal contains Thulsa's research into dividing the Core.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="14" huntingZoneId="72" prevId="13" villagerId="1448">
        <Page social="4">This is Thulsa's experimental journal!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let me flip through it quickly...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Sirjuka Gallery...of course! With the resonance, it makes perfect sense.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What's Sirjuka Gallery?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Sirjuka Gallery...a museum to the ancient magic of the elves. It's so old that most elves don't know of its existence. Some of the objects in the gallery come from a time before the elves had the Core, and they practically vibrate with ancient magic.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If Thulsa was trying to divide or corrupt the Core, it makes sense to use the resonance from even older magic.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Fraya must know this. And it doesn't take a researcher to predict that she'll send you to the gallery.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="15" huntingZoneId="72" villagerId="1448">
        <Page social="0">We must obtain Thulsa's experimental journal.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;And it must be somewhere within Malachai's laboratory.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="16" huntingZoneId="518" prevId="14" villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="4">Sirjuka Gallery?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I knew it! Thulsa's research didn't fail after all.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Find the teleportal to Sirjuka Gallery, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. If you can figure this out, others will figure it out, too.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
