<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="4" huntingZoneId="2" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="202" prevId="0" villagerId="1004">
        <Page social="0">Maon still keeps in contact with the faeries who weren't affected by the mind control magic. After &lt;PCNAME&gt; helps, Maon introduces Lillix.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;By Lillix’s request, &lt;PCNAME&gt; frees Seravy from the dark magic that had taken over his mind. When demigod Volos, the leader of the faeries, finds out what happened, he promised to consider reconciliation between the faeries and the humans.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="202" prevId="0" villagerId="1004">
        <Page social="0">Well, I can tell you that centaurs have some kind of influence over the faeries. But beyond that, I'm at a loss.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Keta might know more. Here, let me mark her homestead on your map. There are so many crossroads that it's easy to get lost.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Take these artful graceblooms with you. Herbs are scarce there, so she'll need them.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="202" prevId="2" villagerId="1046">
        <Page social="4">Who are you? Oh, Verus sent you? No, I haven't discovered anything.&lt;BR&gt;I thought centaurs were pulling the strings behind the faeries, but these centaurs are just as deranged and I'm no closer to finding out why.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Nothing is going as I'd hoped—my investigation has stalled, and I’ve run out of herbs because I used them all to heal the wounded here.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Well, I've got some good news on that front."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Where did you get these artful graceblooms? Ah, that stubborn centurion.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Well, I guess he's not as bad as I thought. I'll make medicine for the wounded. In the meantime, can you go collect some centaur blood? I think it could give me some clues.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="202" prevId="3" villagerId="1046">
        <Page social="4">Excellent. This is just what I need.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If I mix it with this...&lt;BR&gt;And then sprinkle here...&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Are you supposed to mix those?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Oh! Do you see this?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It's a trace of mind-controlling magic. Someone has used mind-controlling magic on the creatures of the forest.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;PCNAME&gt;, go deeper into the forest and find Maon in a cabin. That popori has been an arbitrator for humans and faeries for a long time. Tell him the faeries are cursed by evil magic, and show him this sample. He won't need further explanation.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'll write a letter to Klaon.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="202" villagerId="1046">
        <Page social="0">Are you about to get going?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="202" prevId="4" villagerId="1020">
        <Page social="4">Hmm? What brings you here?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;A sample? What's this a sample of?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"It's proof of what's happened to the faeires."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Oh, a trace of mind-controlling magic! I can't believe I didn't think of that!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The faeries need an antidote, but their biology is different from ours—I can't make an antidote for them.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Here. Take this essence to the faerie pond across the bridge, and find a pixie named Lillix. She can create an antidote for the faeries.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7" huntingZoneId="202" prevId="6" villagerId="1002">
        <Page social="4">Thank you for bringing this.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You know, many spirits thought humans were their enemies. It was Seravy who maintained peace in the forest. But now {@linkcreature:2#206#Seravy} is tainted by evil magic. Without him, spirits are attacking anyone who goes by!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You've got to help {@linkcreature:2#206#Seravy}!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Well, what can I do?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Okay, take this antidote to Seravy. It should cure him.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Unfortunately, you'll need to weaken him, first. Take his strength down to one-third it's normal, then apply.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Once he's cured, lead {@linkcreature:2#206#Seravy} back to the &lt;b&gt;faerie pond&lt;/b&gt;.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8" huntingZoneId="2" villagerId="4">
        <Page social="0">My head is starting to clear up...oh, the state the forest must be in. I've got to set to fixing it.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9" huntingZoneId="202" prevId="7" villagerId="1037">
        <Page social="0">Volos is the commander of the fey forces. He's always been more courageous than wise, but he's no fool. He'll know by my sign that it's time for peace.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Take him this unicorn tear. It's a command he'll obey, even if reluctantly.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="10" huntingZoneId="202" prevId="9" villagerId="1012">
        <Page social="0">This is definitely a unicorn’s tear from Seravy. It’s a relief to know he's free from that spell.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Thanks for all you've done here.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
