<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="99" huntingZoneId="63" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="0" villagerId="1262">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="0" villagerId="1262">
        <Page social="5">&lt;PCNAME&gt;! I wondered when I might see you here!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Rumor has it you're looking for new challenges. Well, your search is over.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The challenge I have is too tough for just one hero, though—even you. Gather some friends, then come talk to me.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="2" villagerId="1262">
        <Page social="5">Ready for that challenge now? Good.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The goal is simple: kill the cyclops in the upper level of the crucible. I said "simple," but it won't be easy.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The foundation level of the crucible contains four outer chambers to the east, west, south, and north. In each, someone must simultaneously protect a spire. Some rooms are better suited to some classes; I'll let you figure out which is best for &lt;PCClass:LCase&gt;s.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But the real key is to protect the final spire in the center hub.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You see why I said to get friends to help, eh?</Page>
        <Page social="5">If, and only if, you've defended the center spire, you and your friends can ascend to the bower and face the real challenge—a series of fights that ends when either you or cyclops dies.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Bring me proof of the cyclops's demise and there's a reward.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When you're ready to go, I can send you to the crucible.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="3" villagerId="1262">
        <Page social="5">The eye of the cyclops? How come you only brought me one?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I kid, I kid. Here's your reward.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Come back tomorrow, or when you're ready to better your score.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="63" villagerId="1262">
        <Page social="0">Talk is cheap, even for a war hero like you. Bring me proof of the cyclops's demise.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
