<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="1" huntingZoneId="453" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="4">&lt;PCNAME&gt;, it has been a long time since we last talked to each other! I hope you have been well.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I have a favor to ask of you. A friend asked me for help, but I cannot leave Elleon just now. I was wondering if you could go there in my place, and help my friend.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I am sure the reward will be well worth your time and effort.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;My friend's name is Penrik. Show him the enclosed letter, and tell him that I recommended you!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;- Jelena</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="75" prevId="2" villagerId="4501">
        <Page social="4">What are you looking at, stranger? Be on your way before you get hurt.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&amp;quot;Jelena asked me to come.&amp;quot;&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">What? Jelena gave you a letter for me?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let me see that.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="75" prevId="3" villagerId="4501">
        <Page social="4">Hmm...I guess you really are Jelena's friend.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Well, it seems I have no other choice. Very well, follow me. But I cannot guarantee you that you will come back in one piece. It’s just that dangerous.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="453" prevId="4" villagerId="4501">
        <Page social="4">Listen carefully, because time is short.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;In the next few minutes, my comrades will arrive with treasure we secured from a stone giant. The giant will be close behind them. We need you to delay the giant long enough for us to move the treasure up the pass.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;My comrades are waiting just on the other side of the barricade. When you're ready, use the lever over here to signal them—then prepare to battle a stone giant!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="453" prevId="5" villagerId="4511">
        <Page social="6">To be honest, I didn’t expect you'd put up much of a fight against the giant, but I have to admit that Jelena chose well. Remind me to buy you a drink some day.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Here's the pay I promised Jelena—and when you see her, give her my regards.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
